#### **Contact**

7383243055 (Work) scm11mishra@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sharutimishra-22a03034 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Recruitment cum

headhunting

Conveyancing Power

Communication

Corporate behavior

analysis

E-commerce activities

**Business Development** 

Performance Management

### Languages

Punjabi English Gujarati Hindi

#### Certifications

Team Star Certificate

Food and drug control administration

Art & craft Certificate

IELTS with 5.5 bands

# Sharuti Mishra

Manager Admin and Hr. at Nationwide PaperAhmedabad

# Summary

Experienced with Recruitment+Talent hunting + client handling + bargaining+ vendor management + Great convincing ability. Although well understanding of corporate atmosphere way of work pattern .. Carrier building in job placement and consulting agencies some werein outsourcing with pen India and abroad, gladly I am part of that journey.

## Experience

#### Nationwide paper Ltd.

Manager Admin and Hr. October

2021 - Present Ahmedabad,

Gujarat, India

- 1. Handling and maintain routine administration, operational routine work of Ahmedabad and uk office.
- 2. HR and recruitment formalities with end to end joining process for uk and India office.
- 3. Retail stores HR work with documentation as well left exercise too performed by me.
- 4. Co-ordinate with uk team members for assigned activities.
- 5. Analysis on products on UK/ US AMAZON and working in listing of new and old product detailed with images and handling queries too.
- 6. Supportive action on customer care department in UK Amazon
- 7. Customer Support exercise within the high time of session globally.
- 8. Continues conversation with team member to short out weekly hurdles of running projects.

### Mahalaxmi dairy (MILKEN BRAND) – Motera dairy Ltd

Branding and promotional Manager November 2019 - May 2021 (1 year 7 months)

Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India

 Looking after admin and Hr. responsibility as well handling Purchase duties with vendor management, supply chain formalities addon dispatch coordination as wellaudit documentation filling excels preparation as per Fssai license, fssc, iso standard.

- 2. Expertise in Branding and Promotional activities with advertising, promotional activities, looking after new and upgraded valuable vendors from local
- 3. Marketing strategy development, online platform updating with new way of ideas, handling team for maintaining goodwill of brand in the market + creating guidelines for resolve issues within shorter time with efficient way.
- 4. Also handling third party vendors, old and new packaging clients with all end to end responsibility of P.O, P.I., billing process as well coordination with account department till delivery of core Products received
- 5. Responsible for new product launches + design selection with Digital media company with new way of creativity in designing and presentation skills
- 6. Handling legal documentation and launching formalities of companies Products in e-commerce
- 7. websites like Flipkart, Amazon, big basket, etc., Looking after all kind of mailing responsibility on behalf of M.D as well brand.

#### Shanti Asiatic School - India

Administration Manager in Shanti Asiatic School (CHIRIPAL GROUP) February 2016 - December 2019 (3 years 11 months) Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India

Handling end to end administration and recruitment part with campus overall responsibility, addon manpower management too in under control our as well PTM Introduction of new syllabus + arrangements of schedule.

#### Trendsetters HR

Sr. Consultant

August 2011 - March 2016 (4 years 8 months)

Ahmedabad Area, India

End to end recruitment cum pure headhunting dealing with MNC clients mostly from Musket, Oman, South Africa etc.,

KG HR Solution pvt ltd HR Head June 2009 - February 2011 (1 year 9 months) Ahmedabad

#### Adecco India

Recruitment team leader

January 2007 - February 2009 (2 years 2 months)

- 1. To search for the resumes at naukri.com as per the need of employees.
- 2. Doing cold calls for the recruitment.
- 3. Take telephonic interviews of the interested candidates.
- 4. Formalities of Appointment and Confirmation letters.
- 5. Daily maintain employee personnel files.
- 6. All end to end joining kit exercise.
- 7. Taking care and watch of the cafeteria at the time of Lunch break and Tea break.

# Education

**Gujarat University** 

M.com, Commerce · (2004 - 2005)

**Gujarat University** 

B.com, Commerce · (2001 - 2004)

Seth R.T High School

12th, Commerce · (1989 - 2001)